Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Lust and Lies=
=الشهوة والكذب=
His son is dead,
ابنه مات
but Huo Beishan has had a celebratory banquet.
لكن هوو بيشان أقام مأدبة احتفالية.
We should be
ينبغي لنا أن نكون
celebrating it instead.
الاحتفال به بدلا من ذلك.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
After Miss Ruan and the Sheng family's marriage alliance,
بعد زواج الآنسة روآن وعائلة شينغ،
the Huo family will have a hard time.
سوف تواجه عائلة هوو وقتًا عصيبًا.
Here.
هنا.
Cheers!
هتافات!
Boss Ruan, this is bad!
يا زعيم روآن، هذا سيء!
The backyard is on fire!
الفناء الخلفي يحترق!
What?
ماذا؟
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
Let's have a toast!
دعونا نحتفل!
Cheers!
هتافات!
Come on.
تعال.
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Do you want
هل تريد
to take a break?
لأخذ استراحة؟
Here.
هنا.
Slowly.
ببطء.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Weilian.
ويليان.
I'm so happy today!
أنا سعيدة جدًا اليوم!
Here.
هنا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Let's have another drink.
دعونا نتناول مشروبًا آخر.
Come on.
تعال.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
♪In a gentle night♪
♪في ليلة لطيفة♪
♪A bare face awaiting blush♪
♪وجه عارٍ ينتظر الاحمرار♪
♪Cups clink, voices overlap♪
♪أكواب تتصادم، أصوات متداخلة♪
♪We switch our roles♪
♪نحن نبدل الأدوار♪
=Episode 18=
=الحلقة 18=
♪Darkness fades, and daylight breaks♪
♪يتلاشى الظلام، ويشرق ضوء النهار♪
♪On the brink of the world's collapse♪
♪على حافة انهيار العالم♪
♪We dance the dance of death♪
♪نحن نرقص رقصة الموت♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I won't let you marry you.
لن اسمح لك بالزواج منك.
Who are you to me?
من أنت بالنسبة لي؟
What gives you the right to mind my business?
ما الذي يعطيك الحق في التدخل في شؤوني؟
You still don't know him.
مازلت لا تعرفه .
Driving him up the wall
دفعه إلى الحائط
will make you lose more.
سوف يجعلك تخسر المزيد.
You should go.
ينبغي عليك أن تذهب.
Leave.
يترك.
Leave already!
إرحل الآن!
The guests are all out there.
الضيوف كلهم ​​هناك.
You should go!
ينبغي عليك أن تذهب!
Now!
الآن!
♪Evening winds usher in the night♪
♪رياح المساء تبشر بقدوم الليل♪
♪On the brink of the world's collapse♪
♪على حافة انهيار العالم♪
♪We dance the dance of death♪
♪نحن نرقص رقصة الموت♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪
Jin.
إحساس.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
I'll make them
سأصنعهم
join you in the afterlife.
انضم إليك في الحياة الآخرة.
Get the camera ready
جهز الكاميرا
for the photo shoot.
لالتقاط الصور.
Qingwan.
تشينغوان.
Come and take some photo.
تعال والتقط بعض الصور.
What are we doing this for?
لماذا نفعل هذا؟
I need to make everyone in Sucheng know my daughter,
أريد أن أجعل الجميع في سوتشنغ يعرفون ابنتي،
Huo Qingwan.
هوو تشينغوان.
The Huafeng Newspaper
صحيفة هوافينج
wants to interview me.
يريد إجراء مقابلة معي.
Last night,
ليلة أمس،
Governor sent his men to get rid of the Huofeng Gang
أرسل الحاكم رجاله للتخلص من عصابة هووفينج
and safeguard Sucheng.
وحماية سوتشنغ.
It's said that bodies were seen floating in the river.
ويقال أنه تم رؤية جثث تطفو في النهر.
Those pirates have all been eradicated.
لقد تم القضاء على جميع هؤلاء القراصنة.
They've all been eradicated?
لقد تم القضاء عليهم جميعا؟
Yes.
نعم.
It's the Huafeng Newspaper's honor
إنه شرف صحيفة هوافينج
to be doing a report
أن أقوم بإعداد تقرير
on such a great achievement.
على هذا الإنجاز العظيم.
You knew it all,
لقد عرفت كل شيء
but you chose to pretend to be ignorant.
لكنك اخترت أن تتظاهر بالجهل.
That was Governor's order.
كان هذا أمر المحافظ.
Huo Xiu.
هوه شيوى.
It's me who can't figure you out.
أنا الذي لا يستطيع فهمك.
Governor made me
الحاكم جعلني
choose between you and the Huofeng Gang.
اختار بينك وبين عصابة Huofeng.
Of course I'd choose you.
بالطبع سأختارك.
I didn't ask you to make the choice for me!
لم أطلب منك أن تختار لي!
I told you so.
لقد قلت لك ذلك.
This isn't the best time for your vengeance.
هذا ليس الوقت المناسب للانتقام.
Fine.
بخير.
You'll stay here
سوف تبقى هنا
and be his lapdog.
وكن كلبه المدلل.
Have you found the locksmith?
هل وجدت القفال؟
There have been some clues about him.
لقد كانت هناك بعض الأدلة عنه.
I've been trying to lure him out, but he hasn't taken the bait.
لقد كنت أحاول إغرائه للخروج، لكنه لم يأخذ الطُعم.
Make it quick.
اجعلها سريعة.
Do you hear me?
هل تسمعني؟
You can open
يمكنك فتح
the Lion Seal by yourself.
أسد البحر بنفسك.
That Japanese man isn't a locksmith, is he?
هذا الرجل الياباني ليس صانع أقفال، أليس كذلك؟
Where is Huo Beishan?
أين هوو بيشان؟
Where is the Lion Seal?
أين يوجد أسد البحر؟
Huo Beishan didn't ask you out.
لم يطلب منك Huo Beishan الخروج.
I did.
فعلتُ.
That's alright.
لا بأس بذلك.
Give me the Lion Seal
أعطني ختم الأسد
and I'll let you have this.
وسأسمح لك بالحصول على هذا.
Hey.
يا.
Why are you
لماذا انت
coveting our valuable?
هل نطمع في ممتلكاتنا الثمينة؟
No one despises money.
لا أحد يحتقر المال.
It's a shame that you're stupid.
من العار أنك غبي.
Don't...
لا...
Don't kill me!
لا تقتلني!
I've been looking for this for more than ten years.
لقد كنت أبحث عن هذا لأكثر من عشر سنوات.
(Yesterday, Governor Huo Beishan of Sucheng led his men to wipe out the Huofeng Gang)
(أمس، قاد الحاكم هوو بيشان من سوتشنغ رجاله للقضاء على عصابة هووفينج)
(His long-lost beloved daughter is found)
(تم العثور على ابنته الحبيبة المفقودة منذ فترة طويلة)
Get me a gun.
احضر لي مسدسا.
Don't try anything funny.
لا تحاول القيام بأي شيء مضحك.
Be it the Ruan family
سواء كانت عائلة روان
or the Huofeng Gang,
أو عصابة هوفينج،
I must get back at him!
يجب أن أعود إليه!
Otherwise, what's the point of pretending to be Huo Qingwan?
وإلا فما الفائدة من التظاهر بأنك هوو تشينغوان؟
Qingwan...
تشينغوان...
Give me a gun.
أعطني مسدسا.
Aren't you afraid she'd get herself killed
ألا تخاف من أن تقتل نفسها؟
by provoking her this way?
من خلال استفزازها بهذه الطريقة؟
No matter how many years
مهما مرت السنين
you've had a dog,
لقد كان لديك كلب،
you need to get rid of it and eat it
يجب عليك التخلص منه وتناوله
when it becomes useless.
عندما يصبح عديم الفائدة.
Miss Ruan.
السيدة روان.
Starting today,
ابتداء من اليوم،
I shall be your teacher.
سوف أكون معلمك.
I'll teach you how to become Huo Qingwan.
سأعلمك كيف تصبح هوو تشينغوان.
You should teach me how to kill.
ينبغي عليك أن تعلميني كيف أقتل.
When you become Huo Qingwan,
عندما تصبح هيو تشينغوان،
I will always be your gun.
سوف أكون دائما مسدسك.
I'll help you with your vengeance.
سأساعدك في الانتقام.
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
♪It whispers of the flame we shared♪
♪همس من اللهب الذي شاركناه♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪